<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
 
 <title>Eli's Blog</title>
 <link href="http://egonzalezjr555.github.io/" rel="self"/>
 <link href="http://egonzalezjr555.github.io"/>
 <updated>2014-09-28T15:26:49-07:00</updated>
 <id>http://egonzalezjr555.github.io</id>
 <author>
   <name>Eli Gonzalez</name>
   <email>egonzalezjr555@gmail.com</email>
 </author>

 
 <entry>
   <title>List of projects working on or planned</title>
   <link href="http://egonzalezjr555.github.io/2014/09/28/new-post"/>
   <updated>2014-09-28T00:00:00-07:00</updated>
   <id>http://egonzalezjr555.github.io/2014/09/28/new-post</id>
   <content type="html">
&lt;h1 id=&quot;list-of-porjects-that-i-am-currently-working-on&quot;&gt;List of porjects that I am currently working on:&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;
		&lt;t1&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/egonzalezjr555/Simple-Arduino-Robot&quot;&gt;Arduino Robot&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/t1&gt;
		&lt;p&gt;While me and my partners still haven&#39;t decided what exactly it is we wish to with this project here is what we have so far. We wish to establish a robot that essentailly can navigate itself. After we find out how we will do this I will add more to that project website.&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;
		&lt;t1&gt;Quadrotor&lt;/t1&gt;
		&lt;p&gt;A project that I am working on with CSE club members at my school. We have just finished with most of it&#39;s physical design and after coming back from a summer we are ready to start programming it. With any luck I will have a link setup shortly once we start with the actual coding.&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;
		&lt;t1&gt;Independent Study at school&lt;/t1&gt;
		&lt;p&gt;I have been talking with a porfessor about this and it seems that I will soon be able to start a project that involves sensors(exactly what I want to learn since it involves electronics/hardware). Once I start I will setup a project page for this.&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
###Note this is only an update a complete list as time goes on hopefully will be added in the &lt;a href=&quot;/projects/&quot;&gt;Projects Page&lt;/a&gt;.
&lt;/ul&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>My first post</title>
   <link href="http://egonzalezjr555.github.io/2014/09/28/my-first-post"/>
   <updated>2014-09-28T00:00:00-07:00</updated>
   <id>http://egonzalezjr555.github.io/2014/09/28/my-first-post</id>
   <content type="html">
&lt;h2 id=&quot;wohooo&quot;&gt;Wohooo&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Finally got it to work I must admit I find this Jekyll along with this Jekyll program that was used to make this message I interesting. I am glad that I spent these last few hours doing this. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Y este es para Cynthia te amo!&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 
</feed>
